by RentAnAdviser.com
Oh‚ hush‚ my dear‚ It is
been a difficult year
And terrors don′t prey
on innocent victims
Trust me‚ darlin′‚ trust me darlin′
It is been a loveless year
I am a man of three fears
Integrity‚ faith‚ and crocodile tears
Trust me‚ darlin′‚ trust me‚ darlin′
So look me in the eyes (Eyes)‚ tell
me what you see (You see)
Perfect paradise (Dise)‚ tearin′
at the seams (Seams)
I wish I could escape it (Escape)‚
I don′t wanna fake it
Wish I could erase it (Erase)‚
make your heart believe
But I am a bad liar‚ bad liar
Now you know‚ now you know
I am a bad liar‚ bad liar
Now you know‚ You are free to go
Did all my dreams never
mean one thing?
Does happiness lie in a diamond ring?
Oh‚ I have been askin′ for
Oh‚ I have been askin′ for problems‚
problems‚ problems
I wage my war‚ on the world inside
I take my gun to the enemy′s side
Oh‚ I have been askin′ for
(Trust me‚ darlin′)
(Trust me‚ darlin′) problems‚
problems‚ problems
So look me in the eyes (Eyes)‚ tell
me what you see (You see)
Perfect paradise (Dise)‚ tearin′
at the seams (Seams)
I wish I could escape it (Escape)‚
I don′t wanna fake it
Wish I could erase it (Erase)‚
make your heart believe
But I am a bad liar‚ bad liar
Now you know‚ now you know
I am a bad liar‚ bad liar
Now you know‚ You are free to go
I can′t breathe‚ I can′t be
I can′t be what you want me to be
Believe me‚ this one time
Believe me
I am a bad liar‚ bad liar
Now you know‚ now you know
Now you know‚ You are free to go
Please believe me
by RentAnAdviser.com